Hello friends, you are very welcome to
your own channel Your Education Account.
Friends, as you all know that the lockdown is
for three months and in this lockdown,
two big announcements have been made by two banks, out of which
one has given a shock and the other has
given us a gift. So let's quickly
know about this update. Friends,
as we all know that the lockdown is applicable in our country for
three months.
During the Lokpal, many changes are being made regarding banking facilities.
Both government and private banks in the country have
given many new features and facilities to the customers,
while by reducing the interest rate on savings, the
savings of the customers are being cut.
Today we will talk about the latest developments made by ICICI Bank and Kotak
Mahindra Bank.
ICICI Bank has given a gift to its customers.
Private sector ICICI Bank has
subscribed through which customers will be
able to get answers to questions including balance, tax, credit card and details. Bank voice assistant best service will be
available 24 hours a day, seven days a week for this facility.  You need to
download Alexa Google Assistant and link it to your ICICI
Bank account through a secure two-factor
authentication process.
After this, customers can ask Alexa Google
Assistant to provide any kind of information,
such as checking balance,
credit card details, or checking F-35 transactions,
etc. Meanwhile, Kotak Bank has
shocked its customers. Private sector
bank Kotak Mahindra has
reduced interest rates on savings deposits for the second time in April.
Earlier, on April 1, savings rates were
reduced in just 20 days.
After the second cut, savings accounts with balances above Rs 1 lakh will get
4.5 percent and those with
amounts up to Rs 1 lakh will get 3.75 percent.
However, if seen,
this rate is still 1 percent higher than the country's largest bank
SBI.
Friends, this was an update from the banks.
You must have liked this video. If you liked the
video, then you must like and share it. If you are
not on the channel, then subscribe to the channel and turn on the
notification button so that
you keep getting notifications whenever I upload a new video.